

KATIE FULLMER designer & developer



ABOUT

Katie Fullmer specializes in designing and developing custom web sites and applications, as well as online and print advertising. With over ten years of experience in web design and development, her broad expertise enables her to utilize a wider range of technologies while delivering custom interfaces that focus on user experience, performance, and functionality. She continually strives to gain experience by challenging herself to stay at the forefront of web technology and standards. She is driven, self-motivated and enjoys the creative problem solving process that web design and development offers.



CONTACT

□ katiegfullmer@gmail.com

www.katiefullmer.com



EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS / AUG 2008 - MAY 2012

College of Art & Design - Louisiana State University Baton Rouge, Louisiana

ART HISTORY MINOR DEGREE / AUG 2008 - MAY 2012

College of Art & Design - Louisiana State University Baton Rouge, Louisiana



EXPERIENCE

HEALTH CONNECTIVE / JUN 2012 - PRESENT

Senior Designer & Front End Developer in New Orleans, LA Provide custom web design and application development, as well as online and print advertising for clients.

BEACHVIEW ENERGY / AUG 2017 - FEB 2020

Freelance Graphic Designer in Brunswick, GA

Provide quarterly customer newsletter layout and designer.

Provide quarterly customer newsletter layout and design, branding and promotional design services.

UTILITY SERVICES - POWER SECURE / JUL 2012 - AUG 2018

Freelance Graphic Designer in Atlanta, GA

Design the company-wide, quaterly newsletter along with a monthly newsletter for the Utility Services division along with other promtional materials.

AMERICAN ALL STAR / MAY 2008 - MAY 2017

Freelance Designer, Camp Director & Dance Instructor in Mandeville, LA Design all promotional media such as brochures, t-shirts, informational binders, & folders.

DIG MAGAZINE / AUG 2011 - JUN 2012

Graphic Designer in Baton Rouge, LA

Design various medias on strict deadlines such as advertisements, posters, media kits, identities, & layouts.

LSU ITS / JAN 2009 - AUG 2011

Information Technology Services Student Worker in Baton Rouge, LA



AFFILIATIONS

AIGA / 2011 - PRESENT Professional Association for Design

DELTA DELTA / 2009 - 2012

Order of Omega

GDSA / 2009 - 2012

LSU Graphic Design Student Association